Eihab Obeidat

Obeidateihab9@gmail.com (+962) 79 154 1142 Github
Portofolio
programming languages:
Javascript, C#, Python, C++, Bash,
JSX, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, SQI

EXPERIENCE

Full stack developer, Freelance

March 2021 to current

- Designed and developed web applications.
- Integrated security measures.
- Designed database structures.
- Managed site functionality & implemented application features.

Cyber security engineer, PTTCT

Aug 2019 to Dec 2020

- Implemented penetration testing and vulnerability assessment projects.
- Maintained office servers, computers, printers, cables and other.
- Implemented pearson VUE authorized Test Center.
- customized backdoors, bruteforce, Web Applications automation tools.

Technical support engineer, ESTARTA

Aug 2018 to Aug 2019

- Troubleshooted voice gateways and unified communication solutions.
- Designed and tested VoIP systems.
- Implemented cisco collaboration technologies.
- · Researched VoIP Protocols.

Trainee, KADDB

May 2018 to Aug 2018

- Performed penetration testing.
- Cyber security researches.
- Simulated cyber-attack to evaluate systems.
- · customized bach scripts.

SKILLS

Frameworks:

- Back-End:
 - Asp.net core
 - NodeJS
 - Flask
- Front-End:
 - ReactJS
 - Angular
- Other:
 - Arduino

DBMS:

- Oracle Database
- PostgreSQL

Technical/programmistic skills

- Web API Programming.
 Agile methodology
- Secure software development.
- Network Engineering.
- PL/SQL
- Bootstrap

- Agile methodology scrum master.
- Proficiency with,
 - Algorithms
 - Data structures
- Other

PROJECTS

Smart House 2021

Convert any facility to a smart one in a very simple, cheap and effective way.

Penetration testing projects

2020

participated in several penetration testing and vulnerability assessment projects for government agencies.

Smart Brain 9

Face detection web application using clarifai AI models, deployed on heroku. react.js used in front-end and node.js, express.js connected by Kenx to the postgreSQL database back-end.

Wireless gesture control robot

2018

A way for helping disabled people, by making movements by hand gesture.

EDUCATION

Jordan University of Science and Technology

2013 to 2018

Bachelor's degree in Networks Engineering and Security

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Four years of experience in information technology. Passionate about software development and engineering. Fast learner with excellent time management and decision-making abilities. Quickly adapts to new technologies and responds to challenges with determination and focus.

Courses:

- Complete Ethical Hacker ZTM
- CompTIA SECURITY +
- CompTIA Network +
- Cisco Certified Network Associate
- Complete Python Developer ZTM
- ISO 27001 Lead Implementer